const level40Questions = [
  {
  question: "Hội trường",
  answers: ["会议厅 (huìyìtīng)", "中心 (zhōngxīn)"],
  correct: "会议厅 (huìyìtīng)",
},
{
  question: "Trung tâm",
  answers: ["中心 (zhōngxīn)", "会议厅 (huìyìtīng)"],
  correct: "中心 (zhōngxīn)",
},
{
  question: "Nhân viên phục vụ",
  answers: ["服务员 (fúwùyuán)", "客人 (kèrén)"],
  correct: "服务员 (fúwùyuán)",
},
{
  question: "Khách",
  answers: ["客人 (kèrén)", "服务员 (fúwùyuán)"],
  correct: "客人 (kèrén)",
},
{
  question: "Người dẫn chương trình",
  answers: ["主持人 (zhǔchírén)", "小伙子 (xiǎohuǒzi)"],
  correct: "主持人 (zhǔchírén)",
},
{
  question: "Chàng trai trẻ",
  answers: ["小伙子 (xiǎohuǒzi)", "主持人 (zhǔchírén)"],
  correct: "小伙子 (xiǎohuǒzi)",
},
{
  question: "Máy quay phim",
  answers: ["摄像机 (shèxiàngjī)", "麦克风 (màikèfēng)"],
  correct: "摄像机 (shèxiàngjī)",
},
{
  question: "Micro",
  answers: ["麦克风 (màikèfēng)", "摄像机 (shèxiàngjī)"],
  correct: "麦克风 (màikèfēng)",
},
{
  question: "Lễ cưới",
  answers: ["婚礼 (hūnlǐ)", "棉袄 (mián'ǎo)"],
  correct: "婚礼 (hūnlǐ)",
},
{
  question: "Áo bông",
  answers: ["棉袄 (mián'ǎo)", "婚礼 (hūnlǐ)"],
  correct: "棉袄 (mián'ǎo)",
},
{
  question: "Cô dâu",
  answers: ["新娘 (xīnniáng)", "新郎 (xīnláng)"],
  correct: "新娘 (xīnniáng)",
},
{
  question: "Chú rể",
  answers: ["新郎 (xīnláng)", "新娘 (xīnniáng)"],
  correct: "新郎 (xīnláng)",
},
{
  question: "Đẹp trai",
  answers: ["帅 (shuài)", "丑 (chǒu)"],
  correct: "帅 (shuài)",
},
{
  question: "Cà vạt",
  answers: ["领带 (lǐngdài)", "西服 (xīfú)"],
  correct: "领带 (lǐngdài)",
},
{
  question: "Không khí",
  answers: ["气氛 (qìfēn)", "热闹 (rènào)"],
  correct: "气氛 (qìfēn)"
}

]

export default level40Questions;